HIMANSHI SAHU

QA TEST ENGINEER







✓ himanshisahuhs@gmail.com

Panvel, Navi Mumbai

SKILLS

Software Testing: Black-box
Testing, White-box Testing,
Regression Testing, Functional
Testing, UAT

Frontend Development: React.js,
JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,
Tailwind CSS

• Backend & Database: MySQL

Automation & Programming: Basic
Java, Selenium WebDriver

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

Shri Balaji Institute of Technology & Mgmt., Betul. (RGPV University, Bhopal)

2011 - 2015

PROFILE

I have 4 years of experience in software testing, specializing in manual testing. My passion for technology has led me to explore development. I have completed an advanced software testing course and am currently learning MERN stack development to build modern and efficient web applications.

EXPERIENCE

QUALITY AND ASSURANCE TESTER

Xanax Technologies

3rd Oct 2022 to 15th oct-2023

- Requirements analysis
- Creation of test cases, checklists and test scenarios.
- Reviewing test cases, updating old ones.
- Performing various testing like regression testing, sanity testing, integration testing, user acceptance testing.
- Producing test reports Communication with the team.
- Automation of some routine tasks for making the work faster using Java+Selenium.

SOFTWARE TESTER

ShujaBITS Infotech Solutions Private Limited

11th Jan 2022 to 30th June-2022

- Requirements analysis.
- Creation of test cases, test plan and test scenarios.
- · Reviewing test cases, updating old ones.
- · Communication with the team

SOFTWARE TESTER

Codestrela Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

1st Jan 2019 to 31st Dec-2021

- Requirements analysis.
- Creation of test cases, test plan and test scenarios.
- Documentation work
- · Mobile Testing.